Sarah Cohen

76 Everit Street ♦ New Haven, CT 06511 ♦ (203) 908-2769 ♦ sarahxcohen@gmail.com

Profile

Motivated, adaptable professional with seven years experience in real estate and finance. Accomplished in quickly mastering new skills. Accustomed to working with several clients and handling confidential information and record databases.

Able to maintain poise and professionalism under pressure. Flourishes in deadline-driven environments and in working on time-sensitive projects. Excellent interpersonal skills.

Skills Summary _

- ◆ Customer Service
- ◆ Written Correspondence
- ◆ Report Preparation
- ◆ General Office Skills
- ◆ Data Entry
- ◆ Critical Thinking/Problem Solving
- Client Relations
- ◆ Extensive Knowledge of Computers & Internet Research
- ◆ Notary Public State of CT

Operating Systems

- ◆ Microsoft Office Suite; Word, Excel, PowerPoint
- ◆ Microsoft Office Outlook
- ♦ ISIS
- ◆ Equator v4 & v5
- ◆ SalesForce
- ◆ Contour
- ◆ DispoSolutions
- ◆ Fiserv
- ◆ The Loan ToolBox

Professional Experience __

CLOSING COORDINATION & ASSET MANAGEMENT

- Work closely with Real Estate Agents, Attorneys, and third party vendors to meet and exceed client goals and expectations for Real Estate Owned (REO) and short sale closings.
- ◆ Close between 90% and 120% of portfolio each month.
- ◆ Conduct one-on-one sessions with Asset Managers to discuss monthly production.
- Oversee day-to-day operations of Pre-Closers.
- Quickly adapt new policies and guidelines in a constantly changing environment.

DETAIL & ORGANIZATION

- Develop and implement Quality Control process for effective file auditing.
 - o Write and maintain instructional training material and Policy and Procedure documents.
- Produce and distribute daily and monthly reports to clients and upper management.
- Prepare financial invoices and assist with accounts receivable.

CUSTOMER SERVICE & FRONT OFFICE OPERATIONS

- ♦ Manage all aspects of day-to-day clerical support in fast paced environment:
 - o Data Entry/maintenance of informational databases.
 - o Appointment setting and follow-up.
 - o Write and edit general correspondence and document preparation
- Undertake Personal Assistant responsibilities for individual employees:
 - Organize events/engagements, run errands, return phone calls.

—Sarah Cohen———————
Employment History
THE NATIONAL GROUPS – Glastonbury, CT Closing Coordinator, 2008 to Present
MAIN STREET MORTGAGE, LLC – Stratford, CT Mortgage Processor, 2005 to 2008
PARADISE REALTY, LLC – Stratford, CT Administrative Assistant, 2005
Education
BENNINGTON COLLEGE – Bennington, VT Literature and Creative Writing, 2004-2005